Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/ drewwaterhouse (LinkedIn) www.teamhammerhouse.com (Company) www.teamhammerhouse.net/ (Portfolio) www.teamhammerhouse.net/ (Portfolio)

Top Skills

Mortgage Banking Mortgage Lending Loans

Drew Waterhouse

Model Match and Hammerhouse have now merged to create the most comprehensive, powerful and award winning recruiting TMS San Clemente

Summary

Drew has been a successful growth and development partner since 1996. He got his start within the technology industry placing highly skilled professionals who built infrastructure and desktop support platforms. In 2001 he used his headhunting skills to develop sales and leadership teams for a national retail mortgage banker. He was instrumental in growing, from the ground up, an in-house headhunting firm, as well as designing concierge and acclimation groups for two national lenders that accounted for organic growth and retention of the sales force and leadership team across the retail, wholesale and correspondent channels. Drew is a dynamic, inspirational and dedicated leader. Outside of his dedication to his partners and employees, he and his wife of 9 years live in San Clemente, CA with their son and daughter. He is actively involved in club auto racing and spending time with his family and friends.

Specialties: Growth by Design. Market intelligence, relationship development, sourcing opportunity that may not otherwise have been evaluated. Finding the right people and helping connect them with the right organization. Model Match and create lasting business relationships.

Experience

Model Match, Inc. (Model Match Software) CRO July 2008 - Present (12 years 11 months) San Clemente, CA

*******Model Match and Hammerhouse have now merged to create the most comprehensive, powerful and award winning recruiting platform in the Financial Services industry!*******

Successful businesses are all about getting the right people on board, nurturing and retaining them. Model Match is helping its client's ace talent management and succeed like never before.

At the core, Model Match has built solutions for managing recruiting activity, tracking lead flow and streamlining candidate hiring and retention. As professional recruiters, we are experts in talent sourcing. Transferring this knowledge to our Award Winning Talent Management System and ultimately our clients, offers them the ability to more effectively prospect and hire the best match. The Model Match solution suite includes Talent Management Software, Best Practice Coaching, Candidate Sourcing based on production, and Full Service Individual and Branch Retained Recruiting Services.

SAND BAR CORAL FARMS, LLC

Partner
December 2017 - Present (3 years 6 months)

About Sand Bar Coral Farms, LLC www.sandbarcoralfarms.com

Coral is our passion. Sustainability is our goal.

About Sand Bar Coral Farms

MISSION VIEJO, CA

Sand Bar Coral Farms is a family owned and operated business located in Mission Viejo, CA, specializing in rare, hard-to-source corals as well as the familiar favorites. Their stock of happy, healthy, and sustainable sourced corals, clams, and invertebrates are meticulously cared for using automated monitoring systems and protocols that allow them to produce consistent stock and set up safe quarantines when needed.

Owners Eric and Darby Perry are proud of their efforts to educate people about reef aquarium husbandry at Sand Bar Coral Farms and through their online forum on Reef2Reef. The farm offers a wide range of free educational workshops to suit beginners and experts. The Sand Bar Coral Farms forum on Reef2Reef is home to helpful dedicated fraggers and enthusiastic noobs who share their knowledge, experiences, and of course, photos of their beloved polyps.

Sand Bar Coral Farms is introducing the Sand Dollar Standard and The Collective to the coral aquaculture community. For this project, Eric and

Darby have brought aboard Drew Waterhouse who is using his expertise in technology, business and sales to take these ideas online with a new ecommerce outlet and an online community for coral enthusiasts.

Hammerhouse, LLC - Strategic Growth Partners
Managing Director, CEO
July 2008 - August 2018 (10 years 2 months)
San Clemente, CA

Hammerhouse, LLC was founded in July 2008 as a national recruiting and strategic growth firm for the financial services industry with mortgage, wealth management and insurance sales and leadership placement at its core. With a decade of experience Model Matching to the Six Core Components of business (Leadership, Culture, Business Model, Operations, Technology & Geography), we support infilling and strategic expansion of more than 12B in annualized production for clients nationally. Our clients are 'best of breed' national, regional and local mortgage bankers and banks, wealth management firms, insurance firms and private equity firms entering and expanding into the market.

What we do:

- Our firm partners with reputable and well capitalized mortgage bankers,
 banks and wealth management & insurance firms nationally as Hammerhouse clients
- Our firm introduces people and companies to each other, who might not otherwise ever meet, ultimately presenting options they might not ever learn about and creating value for all involved.
- Our team is in the 'Culture Matching Business' and help the candidates we represent and clients we work with identify mutually beneficial business partnerships
- Our team consults with financial services producers and leaders to help assess your specific Model-Match based on the Six Core Components of Business (Leadership, Culture, Business Model, Operations, Technology & Geography)

We support our clients nationally through East (North Carolina) and West (Orange County) coast offices, as well as Satellites in Chicago and Redmond, WA.

To join our mailing list, learn more about Hammerhouse, LLC and how Model-Matching can help you achieve your short and long term goals. Indymac Bank SVP, Sales Force Development July 2007 - July 2008 (1 year 1 month) Irvine, CA

American Home Mortgage SVP, Sales Force Development January 2001 - July 2007 (6 years 7 months) Irvine, CA

Direct Source VP, Business Development 1998 - 2001 (3 years) Irvine, CA

Aerotek-TEK systems Senior Recruiter/Account Manager 1996 - 1998 (2 years) Costa Mesa, CA

Education

Chapman University
BS, Business Communications · (1994 - 1996)